{
  "Data": [
    {
      "Question": "A _ is an extremely large group of stars and planets that extends over many billions of light years.",
      "Answer": "Galaxy"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A natural system of medicine, originated in India more than 3,000 years ago.",
      "Answer": "Ayurveda"
    },
    {
      "Question": "There are _ rings on the Olympic flag.",
      "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_ is the largest continent in the world.",
      "Answer": "Asia"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which ocean ‘Bermuda Triangle’ region is located ?",
      "Answer": "Atlantic"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which country, white elephant is found ?",
      "Answer": "Thailand"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The study of weather is called ?",
      "Answer": "Meteorology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who is honoured as Father of Modern Chemistry ?",
      "Answer": "Antoine Lavoisier"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is marsh gas ?",
      "Answer": "Methane"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which is the purest form of carbon ?",
      "Answer": "Graphite"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_ is the smallest ocean in the World.",
      "Answer": "Arctic"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which is the heaviest metal on earth ?",
      "Answer": "Osmium"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The friction in flowing fluid is called ?",
      "Answer": "Viscosity"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the vitamin helps in blood clotting ?",
      "Answer": "Vitamin-K"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which country was Adolf Hitler born ?",
      "Answer": "Austria"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The adult human skeleton is made up of _ bones.",
      "Answer": "206"
    },
    {
      "Question": "_ is a force which tries to pull two objects toward each other.",
      "Answer": "Gravity"
    }
  ]
}
